Hello everyone, we are
We are Nearly Equal Joy!
Yay!
Please.
We are going to take a break due to our schedule, but we have all assembled in the middle of 11 near you.
Yay!
It's been a while.
10 people assembled.
Nice to meet you.
Now that we are all here, let's see what the 11 of us are going to do together,
MiaJoi Ranking Quiz!
This is the MiaJoi Ranking Quiz.
This is a quiz game to guess the ranking of the members, based on the questionnaire from the members and staffs.
Do you remember it?
It was a very exciting game.
In fact, there was a question that was not covered in the distribution due to time constraints.
Now, about half a year has passed since then, and all the members have decided to try it again.
Let me briefly explain the rules again.
We, the members and 12 staff members, will answer a questionnaire asking "Which member do you think is the most ________? We will ask 12 members and staff members to answer a questionnaire that asks "Who do you think is the best member?
You will guess the top 3 ranking from the results of the survey.
You will get 1 point for every rank and for every member you guessed right, and 3 points if you guessed right.
Let's check the hands, shall we?
From the right, Riko and Momotan.
Please take care of them.
We were a pair. We were a pair.
So, Ao and Missky.
Ao and Missky.
Oh, they were a pair.
And Alice and Ayumi.
Ayumi.
They were a pair, weren't they?
And Reno and Mai.
We did it.
And Yuka and Jerry.
Ayumi.
And Ozawa.
Is it really advanced?
Yes. Yes. I want to do my best as a solo writer. Do your best.
I'll do my best.
Well, here is the first issue.
Which member seems to be the best cook?
Who seems to be the best cook?
I don't know.
Maybe even No. 1.
No, it's hard to say.
I'd like to see them in the first or second place.
I think that's a definite.
It's the staff.
Did you guys touch it?
Sleep Boy stage open.
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Oh, man.
One more time.
First place goes to Yuka.
And third place goes to Ganon and Aimi.
Oh!
First place goes to Yuuka.
Garonon in second place
Ai-chan in third place
Onigiri in fourth place.
How is she? It looks like Ai-chan.
Really? Are you happy?
Okay, Ai-chan.
Yuka is first, followed by Ganon and Riko.
Riko?
No, more like Riko.
Is that okay?
Then, Reno.
First place was Yuka, second place was Garonon, and third place was Ai-chan.
That was the third place name.
This is Neimoth.
First place is Yuka, second place is Garonon, and third place is Ayumi.
You say so, don't you?
If I said it the other way around, I'd say Renon in first place, Yuuka in second, and Mitsuki in third.
Just now, I saw Renon in first place,
I had an image of her eating her own lunch, but it was too narrow.
You're so easygoing.
That's right.
Yeah, you don't seem to be doing that.
I do.
I'm the one who's gaping.
Wow!
But we all look alike, don't we?
Yes, they do.
The people who look like you are different.
That's right.
I did it for the look-alike.
Let's see the correct answers, shall we?
Let's see the correct answers.
Today, starting with number 3!
Yeah!
I can do better than that. You look like you could say you're better than that.
Ahhh...
But this is... you look like you're gonna say you're good at it,
Okay?
Not at all.
Are you practicing?
Really, in this case.
I made some hijos.
But I don't do it more than once at Hunter's.
Not by a long shot.
Well, come on, let's tie it up now.
One more this way!
Ew! Ew! Ew!
Oh, man.
I'm so dexterous with everything in my image, this Sasolo.
I'll make a beef stroganoff.
I know, I know.
Do you make beef stroganoff?
We eat it a lot.
I don't know... Today, my mom made me some beef strogano.
I made beef strogano, I have to go home.
I don't make beef stroganoff.
But you have it.
Maybe in the future.
Let's see who's number two.
Here we go.
Wow.
We have a member?
I see.
Because they are lively when they stay over, they often make a pot in an instant, and they are often fertilized with delicious-looking food.
And on an ordinary day, you suddenly make a full-fledged meal for us.
Oh, more like a target?
That's a little strange.
He certainly brought it.
What's with the tempering?
I have to temper it.
Yes, yes, yes.
You have to eat the ganache and the jam and everything inside.
It's so delicious!
Kono-san said that too.
It's not that I seem to be good at it, but I am good at it.
I often hear stories about how good she is at cooking from the other members.
I want to eat RENO's homemade cooking when I drink with him someday!
Okamun
He got 10 votes.
That's amazing!
That's big.
Are they all the same?
He gave me one back.
But you know what?
Everyone gets one point.
Okay, here's the winner of the first place prize.
When was the member?
Sono.
The cutlet that was on social media before looked so good.
Try changing the recipe to this one here.
Do you need the 1 gram of grems in the ingredients?
Yes, I do.
I heard a rumor that Yuka-meshi is very popular among the members.
I want to try it too.
I want omelette rice.
So cute!
It sure is.
And the staff is taking good care of me.
I'm glad.
The yuka rice...
You know what I've been eating, right?
First place goes to Goryoku Velmaid, second to Leno, and third to Yuka.
Alice and Emi pair got 3 points
And the other members of Ivy Guy, 2 points
Me, zero.
Close badges.
Let's go to the second question.
The second question is Akita
Which member is the best fancier?
I can't pick one.
I think they are all good.
Three out of three.
That's good feedback.
I've seen people who can't get all the different versions.
There's nothing good about it at all.
Maybe they're not all really good.
I'm just glad they picked me for this one.
I hope they pick you.
I mean, we'll both be happy even if we come in second.
But second place.
Anyway, I put it on.
I'm done.
Now, let's all open at once!
Ready, set, go!
Oh, here come the good girls!
First place is Aoi, second is Momoka, and third is Aimi.
Yes, we want Momoka in first place, Ai-chan in second place, and Mi-chan in third place.
Ao-chan.
The first place is Konotanbe, the second place is Momoka, and the third place is Aimi.
The first place is Aichan, the second is Aoi, and the third is Maichan.
Oh, maima, maima.
The first place is Aimi.
Number 2 is Momoka and number 3 is Mine.
Yes, I am the key is Key.
2 is Momoka and 3 is Thirty.
I thought it was a bit of an exchange.
I'm sulking that I'm not in.
Interlude
From third place
Third place, tie. Here we go.
Yay!
Yeah!
What?
Yes!
It's hard!
I saw Rinon get on the stage during the show.
I saw Rinon got into her clothes and made her fans while she was dancing and arranging the music.
She's making fans!
I don't know...
When you put your name out there like this
I'm fanning them.
That's nice.
We've got another guy in third place.
Okay, then.
I guess we don't need the third place winner.
Aah!
I'm so happy!
No!
I don't want it!
Asaya.
That's a shepherd.
I'm happy enough just looking at her one way.
If you always look at me with a hoshiya smile...
By Ai.
Congratulations
Asaya.
Congratulations.
for reading about my part-time job.
Thank you.
For writing on my autograph.
That's so cute.
Awesome.
1st place star shop 1st place star shop 1st place star shop
It's my one time.
I have a perda me pair of people.
For sure.
Thank you.
For now, today.
I'll just go with it.
But...
Second place?
This is the second-place member. This is Yurii.
This is Yurii.
With a customer,
She is very good at matching her posture with the audience, and she is giving them eyes to every corner of the stage.
She is also very good at making the audience look at her from all angles, and she is very good at letting the audience enter her sleeve.
They give it to me.
One fan is really good at pleasing them like this.
The members are learning how to do it.
They are good at this kind of thing.
But the ones in the back, they're really good.
Last but not least, we have the first place winner.
Here's the first place winner.
Shut up.
Shut up! Shut up!
The number of fans at the concert was really great.
I thought if I got the number of fans from Momochan, I would like her even more.
Yay!
I'm going to hug you.
Kameko's confidence gave me a perfect fan count.
I have the impression that there are a lot of photos of you addressing them.
Indeed.
That's for sure.
It's more like a picture of Kameko-san's culture.
She has a good eye line, doesn't she?
How did she look at you?
She made an appeal to me.
When I went to a stand or something...
I might be able to see her there.
You might be able to see them there.
You did, didn't you?
That's great!
It's a pure stump pull.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Third place went to Leno and Aimi.
Second place went to Julie, and first place went to Momoka.
So that's one point.
Zero points.
This is a tough one.
It's a very divisive question.
Everyone says so.
Everybody says so.
It's okay.
There's someone else.
And if you look at the looks on their faces, you'll see.
Let's get to the point.
Let's not do that.
Who has the best Oraman accent?
Okay.
Did you guys get it?
I'm on it.
Okay, let's take a step forward together.
Up!
There you go.
Bye.
Hey!
That's everybody!
But, yes, absolutely!
Huh?
Let's see, first place.
Two.
Yeah. - Yeah.
First place goes to Alice, and third place goes to Momoka.
Oh.
We are Rico in first place, Alice in second place, and Momoka in third place.
We are exactly the same.
First place is Rico, second place is Rena, third place is...
You have Rena, too.
First place is Rico, second is Alice, and third is Momoka.
Oh, the same.
First place is Alice, second is Rico, and third is Momoka.
Now, Kiichi, you were lost, weren't you?
I was lost. 1st place is Rico, 2nd place is Alice, and 3rd place is Momoka.
Four pairs of answers are in first place.
Oooh! Fun!!!
It is indeed a different lineup and the biggest is whether Lennon will be ranking.
I will say as little as possible.
Let's look at the 3rd place exine.
This is the girl. Go ahead.
I'm glad.
It's true.
And something else.
Something.
It's true.
I didn't hear you.
If I have trouble with makeup or fashion, I'll ask Momoka.
Because I got angry.
We're the same.
Stop it.
I have this image that everyone asks Momoka about makeup before a concert.
That's true.
I make decisions pretty quickly.
It's partly because I make decisions.
The last member is Matsumoto.
Indeed. I always look like that these days.
Indeed.
I think my clothes are very girly and very cute.
I can arrange my hair and I draw girls' clothes.
Really.
Okay, let's move on to the second place.
Okay, here are the members of the second place. Please.
They're here, they're here.
That's nice.
I don't have the image of them wearing the same clothes, but they are wearing various kinds of clothes, so I think they are well-informed.
That's for sure.
Yes, that's right.
The recording session has just started.
I always ask you about your welfare clothes.
Dresses?
I was wearing a kimono.
And your hair looks Japanese.
Really?
I'm so happy for you, Mr. Igari.
Thank you very much.
Do you have a particular point of interest? Like, what do you always choose?
I always try not to have the same points.
Cute.
Cute with everyone else.
Now then, let's see who will win the first place, the winner of the close battle.
Here is the first-place imema who won a close race.
Oh!
Who is it?
Eeeee!
You did it yourself.
You did it.
Don't you want to see for yourself?
You don't want to look at it?
Probably because I post the most full-body photos on social media,
Rika Fujisawa said.
That's right. Full-body photos.
That's right.
Well, then, you know, it's a little bit inedible, because it's the origin of a unique science and engineering style.
Isn't it hard to match colors?
Pink, green, cotton colors...
This team is amazing!
They got all the questions right!
The ranking was 2nd, Nakabunka and Mai, Alice was 2nd, and Riko was 1st!
So the girl who got all the questions right
gets 1 point!
The winners of 1 point are
Alice, Ayumi, and her sister.
Now the fourth question.
What do you think?
Wow, it's the biggest!
This one might be the biggest.
In the case of time
You know what I mean when I say never.
It's like, you know, you can tell when it's a confirmation system.
You mean a personal line?
It's not personal?
Of course it's personal.
What, like a closed line?
Absolutely not.
Not at all.
But a deadline...
I might be No. 2.
We might be in second place.
I can't decide.
Did everyone write their answer?
Now, let's open everyone's answers at once.
Ta-da!
Here's a picture of the two of them.
Let's see, first place goes to AO, second place goes to Lennon, and the two of you are Nico!
First place is AO, second place is Ayumi, and third place is Lennon.
AO is in first place, Lennon is in second place, and Remi is in third place!
Ayumi is in first place, AO is in second place, and Nico is in third place!
Average?
Average.
Not average.
Ayumi is in first place, Aoi is in second place, and Ganon is in third place.
The first is Ayumi, the second is Ayumi, and the third is Aoi.
But the members who are selected are all alike.
I usually say "Aoi" or "Ayumi" when I am in this area, but I think it was around there.
Ayumi is also surveyed in every survey.
Ayumi, I'm very well informed.
It comes for a moment.
Next?
The second place girl is Kakita!
What? !
Wha!
No!
Oh, no!
Is he sleeping all the time?
Sometimes he doesn't reply as often as I'd like.
It's because I think he's reading my line.
When the transformation comes back, I know it's a long message.
He changes every time he transforms.
He changes for everything.
And the letters are moving.
No, no, no, no.
It's a clean change.
And he always returns important messages.
You really are the king of the red foot.
I've turned you into a mouse, and I don't care if I don't get this back to you as quickly as I should.
As much as I do.
Azusa said she wanted to go to a café with Micchan.
I suggested we go to a café, and she came back with milk.
What?
Mouse is really scary.
Did you lie to me?
I didn't even know you were lying.
My priorities have shifted.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The stock section is so it's either that or ome.
Boo hoo
میی
I'm often out of charge and can't be reached until noon or so.
Can I be sure I'm gonna run out of one? It's going really fast these days.
Isn't this a little old?
That was six months ago.
Have you changed your mind?
I've been preaching to my friends that it's really wrong not to reply.
I got a lecture from a really serious friend.
You're a good friend.
I'm sorry. I'm trying! I'm doing my best.
That's great!
So, if you guys don't get a call from Lennon in the morning, does that mean you're asleep?
Yeah, we're asleep.
Oh, I've seen this before.
And now you're awake.
That's a lot of people.
Does that mean that the batteries ran out in the first place?
No, I'm watching some kind of movie while I sleep.
That's right.
Without recharging.
Watch out.
Sigh... pray... pray...
Pray for a breath... that's how important it is.
The first member is this girl.
It's me.
Me and me.
Myself.
When I want to think for a moment
I often forget.
I tend to leave the line thinking I'll say it when I see you.
I'm sorry!
Life goes slowly and leisurely at its own pace.
Indeed.
I think about what I'm going to say back.
I think about the other person's feelings so much that I end up being late.
You have to be quick.
That's true.
It's Alice!
You can use Alice's picture!
I'm always doing skin-check things.
But I'll be home, even if it's a little late, so...
I'm going to use the numbers, so I'll just go to my cell phone and check.
So, I'm going to do the same thing with the shins in the rankings, and I'm going to do the blue lever, and I want to be number one.
What's going on?
Oh, I'll give you 1234 seconds to decide.
Maisan chose to get 2 points.
Correct! Correct!
Wow!
That's amazing!
What?
Now for the last question.
Here is the last question.
Wow!
Who is the member who seems to have the highest score?
This is terrible.
It looks high.
Hey, hey, hey.
Is that a pan now?
No, no, no.
That was there, too.
Not now.
I already said it.
Yes, you did.
You're lying.
No, thank you, Rust.
I'll give you Rust's answer together.
Open.
Oh!
First place goes to TOMOA
Second place is AOI
MIKI in third place
MIKI in 4th place
MIKI in 5th place
Onowa in first place, AOI in second place, and Yuka in third place
YUUKA-chan.
Really?
Kaz Ono, Yuka, and Aoi came in first, second, and third, respectively.
Aoi is in first place, Kazu Ono is in second place, and Mizuki is in third place.
Aoi in first place, Yuka in second, and Kaz Ono in third.
Oh!
First place is Kaz Onowa, second is Aoi, and third is Yuka.
How could there be no leader?
I'm not a leader.
There is no leader.
I'm...
Let's start from the end.
That's the girl!
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
I got it!
He's not gonna get it all at once, but I'm sure he'll spend some time rewinding before the test.
Oh, yeah.
Well, congratulations on third place!
Congratulations!
I'm in first place, right?
Okay, let's go for second place.
Here's the second place girl.
Oh!
Yay!
Let's do it!
That's great!
Yes!
Yeah!
So, this is what's wrong with people's systems, huh? People decide two weeks in advance.
And they'll have time to review one round before.
That's right. Actually, it was an overnight cram.
I had a high score on all of them.
The scores were high.
I'm curious.
Okay, last premiere.
I'd like to announce the first place winner, and the first place winner is this girl!
Rats breaks
Wow!
Yay!
Amazing! - Wow!
That's great!
This second one
tipo isn't
exudes from every syllable of the conversation.
It's because he's really smart and sometimes when I ask him a question when studying for a test, he answers with a more detailed explanation than in the textbook.
Amazing.
That's amazing.
He sounded like an amazingly intelligent person.
That's the answer.
I'm not a high achiever.
I'm not a high roller.
You're Azuka-chan.
Grandpa.
When you squat like this, it's really...
Eh, yes.
Beam is rhythm
Your blog is great.
I love your blog
Fiam's favorite.
Congratulations!
So the 3rd place goes to
I'm going to go ahead and say that second place is Yuu or first place is
You!
So...
There was a sequential numbering system, wasn't there?
One point left.
One point.
Ede no Umito and
Alice, you have 1 point for the Yumi pair.
Oooh
So that means
Not at all
The problem is over!
OH!
Now, the RICO&OMOKA team has 7 points
And the AO&MITSUKI pair has 7 points
Oh!
And, ARIS&AYUMI pair with 7 points
OH!
And, RENO&MY TEAM pair with 8 points
Strong!
And, YUTA&JULIE pair has 10 points
OH!
Yay!
And, AYUMI&YO-MOIN 7 points
So, the winning pair is YUTA&JULIE pair
Oooh!
Congratulations!
How do you feel now that you have won?
A little...
What?
It's great.
Okay, so this is the first time in about six months
It's been about 6 months since I've done a member rifle.
I did a comic book!
Great!
It was a lot of fun!
So, if you liked this video, please
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a good button!
Thank you very much!
Enjoy the next video!
Bye bye!
Bye bye bye
Bye-bye!